Guide to the Duke University Oral History Program Collection, 1973-1978, 1992 RL.00338
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- North Carolina Civil Rights Movement, 1973-1992; 1
  - Harris, Maggie Scott - interviewer unidentified, 1974-01-31; 58
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0256)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0371)
  - Hathaway, Allen; Rushing, Emanuel - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1977-11-04;1977-11-05; 59
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0098)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0009)
  - Hicks, Charles; Farrell, "Tink" - interviewed by Leon Fink, 1974-06-08; 60
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0258)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0373)
  - Hill, George Watts - interviewed by William Chafe, Wendy Watriss and Lois Gilman, circa 1974; 61
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0259)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0374)
  - Hill, Watts Jr. - interviewed by William Chafe, 1974-06-14; 62
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0260)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0375)
  - Hilliard, I.H. - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1977-05-07; 63
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0099)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0010)
  - Hudgens, Eula - interviewed by William Chafe, 1974-12-17; 64
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0261)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0376)
  - Hughuely, Sadie - interviewed by Harriott Quin, 1977-12-02; 65
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0262)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0377)
  - Jarrett, Hobart; Edmonds, Edward - interviewed by William Chafe, circa 1974; 66
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0243)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0360)
  - Jones, Charles - interviewed by Ken Hamilton and Sklar, circa 1974; 67
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0265)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0380)
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0263)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0378)
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0264)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0379)
  - Kerley, Jack - interviewer unidentified, 1976-01-16; 68
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0266)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0381)
  - Khazan, Jibreel (formerly Ezell Blair, Jr.) - interviewed by William Chafe, 1976-11-27; 69
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0267)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0382)
  - Klopfer, Peter - interviewer unidentified, 1976-06-05; 70
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0268)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0383)
  - Lassiter, Gaitha - interviewed by Tina Harrison, 1974-08-21; 71
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0269)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0384)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0270)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0385)
  - Lee, Howard - interviewed by Fred Baldwin and Tina Harrison, 1974-08-27; 72
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0271)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0386)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0272)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0387)
  - Lineberry, Al - interviewed by William Chafe, 1974-12-17; 73
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0273)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0388)
  - Malone, C.C. - interviewed by Lois Gilman and Ken Hamilton, 1974-08-23; 74
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0274)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0389)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0275)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0390)
  - Manley, J.R. - interviewed by Ken Hamilton, Tina Harrison and Wendy Puriefoy, 1974-06-11; 75
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0276)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0391)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0277)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0392)
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0278)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0393)
  - Mark, Carolyn - interviewed by William Chafe, 1974-10-10; 76
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0279)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0394)
  - Matthews, Mrs. A.C. - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1976-10-08; 77
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0100)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0011)
  - McClamrock, Sandy - interviewed by William Chafe and Fred Baldwin, 1974-06-06; 78
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 3 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0280)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 3 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0395)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 3 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0281)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 3 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0396)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 3 of 3 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0282)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 3 of 3 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0397)
  - McCoy, Cleo - interviewed by William Chafe, 1977-09-06; 79
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0283)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0398)
  - McDougall, C.A.; McDougall, Mrs. C.A. - intervewed by Ken Hamilton and Tina Harrison, 1974-06-05; 80
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0284)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0399)
  - McLaurin, Bessie - interviewer unidentified, 1973-04-20; 81
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0285)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0400)
  - Morehead, David - interviewed by William Chafe, 1974-12-19; 82
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0286)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0401)
  - Moseley, Alexander - interviewed by Harriott Quin, 1977-11-28; 83
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0287)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0402)
  - Moseley, Leroy - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1976-11-05; 84
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0101)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0012)
  - Osborne, Robert - interviewed by Hugo Leaming and Reginald Kearney, 1974-06-04; 85
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0288)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0403)
  - Perry, Velma - interviewed by Janice Carr, Elinore Ramsey and Wayne Watson, 1974-06-06; 86
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0289)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0404)
  - Phelps, Jake - interviewed by Tina Harrison and Lois Gilman, 1974-06-06; 87
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0290)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0405)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0291)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0406)
  - Phelps, Jon - interviewer unidentified, 1973-03-28; 88
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0292)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0407)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0293)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0408)
  - Queen, Anne - interviewed by Wendy Watriss and Lois Gilman, 1974-06-11; 89
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0294)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0409)
  - Rev. Sada - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1976-11-05; 90
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0105)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0016)
  - Reverend Jones - interviewed by Ken Hamilton and Sklar, undated; 91
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0253)
  - Richardson, John - interviewed by Dick Landeman and Leon Fink, 1974-06-07; 92
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0295)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0410)
  - Robinson, Lousiana - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1976-11-06; 93
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0102)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0013)
  - Rorie, Magdalene Gillespie - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1977-05-01; 94
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0103)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0014)
  - Ruffin, Ben - interviewed by Harriott Quin, 1977-12-06; 95
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0296)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0411)
  - Rushing, James - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1976-11-04; 96
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0104)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0015)
  - Sanford, Terry - interviewed by Wendy Watriss and Lois Gilman, 1974-08-29; 97
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0297)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0412)
  - Schumaker, Jim - interviewed by Fred Baldwin and Wendy Watriss, 1974-06-06; 98
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0298)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0413)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0299)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0414)
  - Scroggs, Ross - interviewed by Lois Gilman, 1974-08-07; 99
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0300)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0415)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0301)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0416)
  - Shepherd, Ann; anonymous - interviewed by Larry Thomas, 1978-07-10;1978-07-11; 100
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0118)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0029)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0121)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0032)
  - Sieber, Hal - interviewed by William Chafe, 1974-11-08; 101
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0150)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0061)
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0302)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0417)
  - Smith, David - interviewed by Hugo Leaming, 1974-06-06; 102
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0151)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0062)
  - Smith, Reginald - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1974-06-13; 103
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0153)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0064)
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0152)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0063)
  - Snider, William - interviewed by William Chafe, 1976-11-09; 104
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0154)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0065)
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0155)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0066)
  - Spearman, Walter - interviewed by Fred Baldwin and Lois Gilman, 1974-06-05; 105
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0156)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0067)
  - Straley, Joe - interviewed by Lois Gilman, 1974-08-17; 106
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0157)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0068)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0158)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0069)
  - Strowd, Gene - interviewed by Fred Baldwin, 1974-08-27; 107
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0159)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0070)
  - Sturdivant and Jones, Carrboro Barber Shop - interviewed by Dick Landeman, 1974-06; 108
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0160)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0071)
  - Templeton, Eugene - interviewed by Larry Thomas, 1978-08-01; 109
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0119)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0030)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0120)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0031)
  - Timberlake, Phyllis - interviewed by Wendy Puriefoy and Alphine Jefferson, 1974-06-05; 110
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0161)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0072)
  - Unidentified -, undated; 111
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0171)
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0172)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0082)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0083)
  - Wager, Paul - interviewed by Lois Gilman, 1974-08-07; 112
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0162)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0073)
  - Walker, James R. - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1976-10-07; 113
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 3 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0106)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 3 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0017)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 3 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0107)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 3 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0108)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 3 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0018)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 3 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0019)
  - Wallace, James - interviewed by Lois Gilman and Wendy Watriss, 1974-06-12; 114
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0163)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0074)
  - Walters, Adelaide - interviewed by Wendy Watriss, 1974-06-10; 115
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0164)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0075)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0165)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0076)
  - Weaver, Preston; Smith, Reginald D. - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1977-05-03; 116
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0109)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0020)
  - Weaver, Susie - interviewed by Wendy Puriefoy, 1974-06-06; 117
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0166)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0077)
  - Williams, P.A. - interviewer unidentified, 1973-12-19; 118
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0167)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0078)
  - Wilson, Hugh - interviewed by Wendy Watriss and Reginald Kearney, 1974-06-05; 119
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 3 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0168)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 3 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0079)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 3 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0169)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 3 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0080)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 3 of 3 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0170)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 3 of 3 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0081)
  - Wilson, Woodrow - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1977-04-30; 120
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0110)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0021)
  - Winfield, B.J. - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1977-05-01; 121
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0111)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0022)
  - Yopp, Abbot D., Jr. - interviewed by Tim Tyson, 1992-08-15; 122
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-MCS-0001)
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0149)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0060)
- North Carolina Miscellaneous, 1973-1975; 2
  This series includes an interview with Alex Haley about his book Roots, recordings of William Chafe dictating a letter to the Mary Reynolds Babcock Foundation and a study of communal living, discussions with international students at Duke University, and interviews dealing with agriculture in the state and with traditional mountain life and culture in Western North Carolina.
  - Chafe, William; dictation of a study of utopian communal living -, undated; 123
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0136)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0047)
  - Chafe, William; dictation of letters to William Archie and William Bondurant of the Mary Reynolds Babcock Foundation (Winston -Salem, NC) -, undated; 124
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0135)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0046)
  - Haley, Alex - interviewer unidentified, 1973-02-06; 125
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0141)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0052)
  - Hyatt, Mrs. W; Nix, M.C. - interviewed by Karen Hammett, on education and mountain culture, 1974-03; 126
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0142)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0053)
  - International students on U.S., business grad. Student at Duke from Madras, India, Duke student from the Philippines -, 1974; 127
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0138)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0049)
  - International students on U.S., Duke professor (former student) from Canada, Duke student from Hong Kong -, 1974; 128
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0137)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0048)
  - International students on U.S., Duke student from Hong Kong, Duke student from Philippines -, 1974; 129
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0139)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0050)
  - International students on U.S., Duke student from the Philippines, Duke graduate student from Australia -, 1974; 130
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0140)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0051)
  - Leatherwood, Lawrence; McCracken, Elise - interviewed by Karen Hammett, on education and mountain culture, 1974-03; 131
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0143)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0054)
  - Mitofsky; CBS research, contemporary U.S. -, 1975-05; 132
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0144)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0055)
  - Silberman; Duke prof., administrator's opinion on the formation of the Institute for Policy Sciences -, circa 1973; 133
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0145)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0056)
  - Strothers, Kerman C.; agriculture in Wake County 1950s -1970s, economic and business development in Apex -, 1974-01-23; 134
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0146)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0057)
  - Tunstall, Warren; agriculture in NC, 1950s -1970s -, 1974-01-19; 135
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0147)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0058)
  - Wheeler - interviewed by Gene Walker, 1974-04-03; 136
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0148)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0059)
- Tulsa Race Riots, 1978; 3
  The Tulsa Race Riot interviews were conducted by Scott Ellsworth in 1978. These thirteen tapes were part of the basis for his 1982 book, Death in the Promised Land: the Tulsa Race Riot of 1921.
  - Caruthers, B.E. - interviewed by Scott Ellsworth, 1978-07-21; 137
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0127)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0038)
  - Duckery, Nathaniel - interviewed by Scott Ellsworth, 1978-06-13; 138
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0126)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0037)
  - Fairchild, Robert - interviewed by Scott Ellsworth, 1978-06-08; 139
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0124)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0035)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0125)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0036)
  - Hodge, Victor H. - interviewed by Scott Ellsworth, 1978-06-12; 140
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0128)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0039)
  - Jones, Mozella Franklin - interviewed by Scott Ellsworth, 1978-06-20; 141
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0123)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0034)